Thank you.
You're the only person
who made this occasion special for me.
You were threatened and scared.
I can't leave you. I'll protect you.
Someone is scaring me!
The entire campaign is canceled.
But we shouldn't stop looking
for whoever leaked the campaign.
You want to eliminate the person
who's protecting me
from everything.
That trust is making you soft…
Ms. Diana Aragon.
I've got Diana wrapped around my finger.
She falls in love with me
and she won't be able to escape.
-Teddy.
-What are you doing here?
I just want to ask you something.
What makes you think
I'd cooperate with you?
No.
I didn't talk to that reporter.
I didn't answer his questions.
Why would I give information
that could hurt my own family?
We have another piece of evidence
against you.
You are suspended effective immediately
for leaking confidential information
to a rival company.
I want to talk to my sister.
This is a setup.
You will be summoned
for an administrator hearing
-so you can defend yourself.
-You!
-Let go of me!
-Sir, calm down!
I know you're behind all of this!
You set me up! You'll pay for this!
Just you wait!
Let me go! Hey!
Let me go!
Let me go! You'll pay for this.
Ricardo, come back here!
Let me go!
You won't get away with this!
I'll make you pay!
Let me go!
Hey, Patricia. Give me one too.
Thank you.
We told you we should
each make our own copies.
It's cheaper
at the computer shop near my place.
You're amazing, Patricia.
You're juggling so many things at once.
Don't you still have work after class?
Do you even get to rest?
Of course!
-Can you hand these out?
-Sure.
We don't have class every day.
So I just do everything I can
when I have the time.
Buy my toasted buns during break, okay?
-Oh, sure.
-Sure.
I made a lot of copies.
-Good morning.
-Good morning, ma'am.
Good thing you have the handouts now.
You're amazing, Patricia.
Your classmates really
look up to you as a leader.
I'm glad I could help, ma'am.
I make money on the side too.
I can see you're a good organizer.
Would you like
to head the student committee
for our upcoming Entrepreneurship Week?
And this will have credits on your grades.
Sure, ma'am! I'll do it!
I have one more favor to ask.
We would like to send
a letter of invitation
to Ms. Diana Aragon.
We'd like to invite her
to speak at the event.
I hope you can convince her.
Okay, ma'am.
Your mother is an excellent businesswoman.
She's one of the best and most inspiring.
The students could learn so much from her.
-Okay, ma'am.
-Okay.
Okay, let's start!
I want all your decks this afternoon.
And I want them different
from the previous campaign, okay?
Not the slightest detail.
Yes, Ms. D!
I'll check your works later.
Yes, sir.
-Enzo.
-Yes, ma'am?
Where's Patricia?
Does she always come late?
No, Ms. D. It's just for today.
Hasn't she told you?
About what?
Uh…
Patricia, why are you late?
I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
All right. Just go and finish
what you need to do.
Yes, Ms. D.
Ma'am, have you seen the slides
I sent you?
I'll get into it.
Okay, ma'am.
Excuse me.
Enzo.
Is Patricia going through something?
It would be better
if she tells you herself, Ms. D.
Enzo… spill it.
She came from class.
She doesn't want you to know,
but I think you should.
Patricia's gone back to school.
Hey, hey!
-Are you okay?
-Mm-hmm.
It's nothing.
You feel a bit feverish.
No, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Why are you still here?
I had to finish something.
I was just taking a break.
Please don't tell Ms. D about this.
She might get mad at me again.
I don't want to add on to my sins.
Why don't you just tell her
that you've gone back to school?
She'd understand that.
She might even help you
adjust your schedule.
I don't want any special treatment.
What is it?
Ms. D needs some documents
for Burger City.
She wants them taken to her house tonight.
But I've got something else to do.
I'll do it.
-You don't have to.
-It's okay. You need to rest.
I still need to make up
for my mistakes before.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
-T-take care.
-Mm.
Oh! Patricia. Come in, come in.
Mm.
Perfect timing.
I just finished cooking.
You should stay for supper.
I'm not here to visit, Nanny Cora.
-Huh?
-It's for work.
I'm going home right after.
But why?
Um…
I just came to deliver
these files to Ms. D.
-Can you give these to her?
-Oh.
Why don't you give those to her yourself?
But…
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I'm probably just nauseous from the trip.
Oh, you're not fine. Come, have a seat.
Come on. Sit over here. Come on.
Oh-- Oh! Patricia!
Pat-- Help!
Help-- Patricia!
Help! It's Patricia!
-What happened?
-Patricia!
-What happened? Patricia!
-She suddenly fainted!
-Patricia!
-She's burning up!
Benjie! Benjie!
-Be… Benjie!
-Ms. D?
-Bring her to the guest room.
-Okay.
I HOPE YOU CAN GET
SOME REST NOW. GOOD NIGHT.
I have told you several times.
Quit football!
I've done nothing but work
to feed you!
Mom.
What happened?
I want to go back there.
I want to be with you.
Did your father hit you again?
Mom, didn't you say
you're going to take me from him?
Don't worry, okay?
Mom will do everything
to get you back from your father.
But, son, I can't do it right now.
Just hang in there a bit more.
Mom, I can't do it anymore.
If you put your mind to it,
you can do anything.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Ricardo.
I miss you.
Why did you come home?
I traveled all the way from Indonesia.
You didn't even pick me up,
and this is the welcome I get?
I thought you understood the situation.
I do.
But, of course,
I want to spend time with you.
From now on, I'll be staying
in the Philippines.
So that we can be together.
But you know what my plans are, don't you?
Don't worry, I won't stand in your way.
Use me however you want.
I owe you so much.
l will help you.
I'm finally on her good side.
I make her smile even when
she's dealing with problems.
It's like she hasn't ruined any lives.
YOU'RE GOING TO PAY!
WHO'S THIS? I'LL CALL THE COPS!
YOU DON'T SCARE ME!
I'LL FIND YOU! I'LL SUE YOU.
She doesn't know what's coming for her.
I'll take everything from her.
She's going to pay
for what she did to my mother.
Diana isn't easy to break.
But just a little more,
and she'll be mine.
I've worked hard to find my way
into Diana Aragon's life.
Even Patricia, I've already tamed.
I have them in the palm of my hand…
while I make Diana suffer
little by little.
Just like how you
and your mother suffered.
Even worse.
Son, I have some good news for you!
I got into a big company! La Familia!
Really, Mom?
Congratulations, Mom!
My son…
This is the start of a new life for us.
Once everything is settled,
I'll take you home.
We'll be reunited, son.
Mom, I can't wait for that day to come!
My situation here is a bit
complicated right now, son.
But I'll save up.
Mom!
Son, I just need to take care
of something, alright?
I have to look after your siblings.
My husband is arriving soon.
Son…
I'll make it up to you.
It won't be long now.
Just a little more patience, alright?
So that's it. Thank you for today, guys.
Congratulations again, Ricardo.
This is your best work so far.
Thank you.
I'm sure you will
get another promotion soon.
Celebrate tonight?
Thank you, but… probably next time.
-We'll go ahead.
-All right.
-Thank you.
Hello, Mom?
Is this Cecilia Pineda's son?
I'm calling from Saving Grace Hospital.
Something happened to her.
If no one in your family
started the fire, then who did?
Cecilia Pineda!
A disgruntled employee
who holds a grudge against our company.
A lot of people know this.
We have witnesses testifying against her.
Son, help me.
They're going to put me in prison.
Help me, son.
Mom, you're innocent.
After everything they did to me,
I'm the one who has to suffer?
I won't let them lock you up, Mom.
I'll help you escape.
Son, it hurts so much!
Hang in there, Mom.
The captain has been paid, sir.
We've also informed
our contacts in Indonesia.
But they might ask for more money.
This isn't exactly easy.
Name your price.
Just get us out of this country.
Here are the fake medical
transfer papers you requested.
The other documents are included too, sir.
You're all set now.
The supposed body of your mother
has already been arranged for burial,
so they'll stop coming after you.
Mom, Sandra has already
prepared all that you need.
I have to get to work.
So much time has passed,
but you haven't kept
a single promise to me.
Do you think my life here is easy?
I've been suffering for years, Ricardo.
But they just get to move on
with their lives.
Mom, I'm just taking care of something.
So I'm focusing on your recovery
because you're sick.
i want you to live longer.
What's the point of me living?
The people who did this to me
are living comfortable lives.
Mom, I would do anything for you.
Make sure you stick to our agreement.
You know what you have to do.
Put this in the Cala Soda bottles
that'll be delivered
to the feeding program.
Do a clean job, understand?
Yes, sir.
I can already see her downfall.
I'll make sure she suffers
the way we suffered.
I'll make her suffer
even more than we did.
-Hey, Enzo.
-Nanny Cora.
-Come in.
-Is Patricia still here?
Oh, um, she's burning up with a fever.
She didn't make it home last night.
She's upstairs resting.
-I see.
-Yes.
Enzo, what are you doing here?
Ms. D, good morning.
They're looking for Patricia at her place.
I just came by to check on her.
Is everything okay?
I've already informed her father.
Is there anything I can do?
I can go out.
I can buy medicine, food, anything.
No, it's okay, Enzo.
We'll take care of Patricia.
You can go back to La Familia.
Did you come here for me… or for Patricia?
I'm just worried about Patricia, Ms. D.
Because?
Because she's sick.
Because…
Well, Ms. D, I…
I care for your daughter.
And why?
I like her, Ms. D.
I like Patricia.
This is not the right time.
Patricia has a lot of things
to fix in her life.
Don't make it complicated.
Don't go there.
Hm?
With all due respect, Ms. D…
I'm just telling you this to inform you.
I think we are at the right age.
And I think Patricia should be
the one to make those decisions.
Go back to La Familia.
Here's Patricia's phone.
She forgot it in the office.
Have a great day, Ms. D.
Oh, Martin, where are you going?
To the mansion.
Patricia's there, and she has a fever.
Come on, you.
Patricia's not a kid anymore.
Plus, I'm sure you'll just fight
with Diana when you see each other.
It's not like I can just
leave her all alone.
Why? Is her condition that bad?
Don't get me started.
Are you really going there for Patricia?
Or Diana?
What is this? A family reunion?
You're both going to take care
of your beloved daughter?
What? Martin.
Patricia.
Why did you get up?
You're still recovering.
I'm fine.
What happened?
You fainted.
Your fever was so high last night.
My gosh. Here.
We prepared some breakfast for you.
Eat it first.
When you finish, change into these, okay?
Come. Eat up.
Goodness me.
-Come!
-Oh, you shouldn't have bothered, Nanny.
Mm-hmm?
Oh, no.
Ms. D will surely get mad at you.
You know how she is.
She doesn't like the smell of dried fish.
I even troubled you last night.
What are you even talking about?
Diana requested this herself.
She told us to cook for you
because she knows these are your favorite.
Go on, eat up.
Mmm.
Were you the one
who took care of me last night?
I'm sorry for the trouble I've caused you
but thank you.
Don't thank me.
Thank your mother.
She's the one who took care of you.
She even slept by your side.
All night long, she looked after you.
I'll show you something.
Here.
I'll head in first.
No matter how many years have passed,
she didn't change anything.
Not a single thing.
She wanted this room to stay the same way
as you last saw it.
Maybe there's something in here
that you like.
You can take it home.
It's yours anyway.
I'll talk to your mother.
Why are you here?
Where's…
Nanny Cora?
My room hasn't changed at all.
I didn't change anything.
In case you came back.
But I didn't expect that…
we'd be separated for so long.
It's been a while since…
I last went in here.
It's a waste of space.
You could've turned it
into your home office.
I want you to have somewhere to return to.
Uh…
You're the one
who took care of me last night?
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
But thank you.
I know…
I wasn't a good mother to you.
But I hope you believe that…
I tried.
It may not have been enough.
But that doesn't mean that I haven't…
fought for you.
Where's my daughter, Cora?
Call your boss.
Martin, just wait.
-They're going down.
-Don't say too much. Call your boss!
-Dad.
-Patricia.
What are you doing here?
You should've just taken Patricia home.
I can take care of her.
I can get her treated.
We don't need to argue about this.
Just say it,
you just want to rub it to my face
that I can't take care of Patricia.
Right?
What are you trying to pull?
I'll do what I did
as many times as I have to for Patricia.
Maybe you've forgotten.
We're living this kind of life
because of you.
Because you abandoned us.
Patricia begged you back then, didn't she?
But what did you do?
You drove her away.
You even dragged our child
into your anger toward me.
And now, you're going to pretend
to be the perfect mother.
You don't know the truth, Martin.
What do you mean, "I don't know"?
Now you're painting me
a liar in front of Patricia?
I helped you, Martin.
Because my daughter asked for it.
What do you mean?
Diana, Martin got into an accident!
Mom, let's go. Let's go!
-They don't want us here!
-No, wait!
They don't want us!
-Diana!
-Please leave, Carlota.
Please, Diana!
Mom, let's go!
Diana.
What does she need?
She said Martin got into an accident.
She stole my husband,
now she'll come to me for help?
You didn't see Patricia.
Patricia?
-Is she there?
-They've already left.
Carlota Cervantes?
Ma'am Diana Aragon sent these
for Sir Martin.
For his operation.
-These are from Diana?
-Yes.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
That's not true!
You're losing your mind.
Carlota was the one who found a way
to help me.
Then ask her.
Come on, dear. Let's leave.
Patricia!
Thank you.
Carlota!
I'm glad you're home.
Patricia, are you still sick?
Jena, leave us alone for now.
Carlota, let's talk.
What do you want to talk about?
Hm?
You want to talk
about how you and Diana reconciled?
Is that what his is about?
-Tell me--
-From whom…
and where did you really get the money
for my hospital bills?
Why do you keep bringing that up?
Didn't I tell you before?
I borrowed money from my acquaintances.
I did everything I could.
I lined up, I-- I sought help
from the government.
Who did you borrow from?
What is this?
What? Do you want a name?
Do you want a list?
Do you want me to name them one by one?
-Huh?
-Diana said…
-What?
-she gave you the money.
You made us believe
that she didn't help Dad.
Fine!
All right!
Fine, the money came from her.
But that doesn't erase
how terrible she was.
She abandoned you.
But me?
I spent almost my whole life
devoted to you!
I took care of you.
I sacrificed so many years for you,
and this is how you repay me?
You're going to throw it in my face?
It wouldn't have gotten this bad
-if you had told us the truth!
-Fine, then! Fine!
Fine! Take each other's side!
Go back to her if what I did was so wrong!
If you think I've never
done anything right,
then fine! I'll be the villain!
Diana. What's happening?
I don't know what you're accusing me of.
I didn't do anything wrong.
The evidence against you is clear, Teddy.
Face the investigation. Prove to them…
-that you're innocent.
-Why won't you believe me?
I'm your brother. I'm your family.
Why does what other people say
matter more to you?
Family? Why? Since when has that
become important to you?
You don't even listen to my side!
Come on!
I gave you so many chances.
And each time, you have proven me wrong!
When did you ever trust me?
Even then, no matter what I do,
you're always doubting me.
You treat every mistake
like it's a mortal sin.
Like it'll ruin your whole world.
Have I ever done
anything right in your eyes?
Don't turn this around on me, Teddy.
You're no different than Dad.
That's why Mom left him.
He's evil to the core.
Aren't you afraid
you'll end up just like him?
Oh, wait! I'm sorry.
You already are!
Even worse!
Since you were a child,
I was the one who took care of you.
But you never saw that.
Because you never saw me as your sister,
but only as your competition!
What's on your mind?
You've been deep in thought for a while.
I thought she had completely
erased me from her life.
I resented her for so long, Enzo.
But all this time…
she was just waiting for me to come home.
Sometimes, you just have
to be open, Patricia.
Does that mean…
you two are okay now?
Not right away.
But I'll try.
-Good morning.
For you.
What's this?
Vitamins.
Oh.
Thank you.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay now. You don't have to worry.
You're…
You're back in school?
How did you…
Enzo told me.
Can you juggle both work and school?
Just let me know.
We can arrange a special schedule
to accommodate your studies.
Oh no, that's not necessary.
I've got it figured out.
Uh…
I know this is late, but…
I wanted to say thank you
for helping with my dad.
He could've been left disabled
-if you hadn't helped him.
-Oh.
Patricia…
Let's forget about that.
Let's just move on.
You're right. Move on.
If there's anything I can help with
or if you need anything,
please let me know.
To be honest, I do need something.
Good thing, you asked.
What? Tell me.
It's…
There's a school activity
that I was assigned to.
It's for our Entrepreneurship Week.
-Ah!
-Uh…
I wanted to invite you there.
Just tell me when
and I'll adjust my schedule.
You'd do that?
Yes!
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
I'll see you later?
-Yes.
-Okay.
Uncle Teddy?
I just want to talk to you.
Listen to me.
Talk to my sister for me.
Tell her I am not guilty.
Uncle Teddy,
if she doesn't believe in you,
I can't do anything about it.
This is all Ricardo's doing!
He's the one to blame!
He's spreading rumors about me!
He framed me,
he set me up, he was the one to blame!
Not me!
Why would I believe you?
And why would Sir Ricardo do that to you?
I don't know. All I know is he has a plan.
So, you want me to talk to Ms. D
because of your hunch?
I just know that he wanted
me gone from La Familia.
Patricia, I'm innocent.
What if you don't really know Ricardo?
I guess Sir Teddy must be so desperate
to talk to you about that.
But why was he saying that Sir Ricardo
was the one framing him?
No. That would be weird.
Why would Sir Ricardo do that?
Before he got in La Familia,
Ms. D and I did a background check on him.
I didn't see anything
questionable about him.
I know that Uncle Teddy
has every reason to lie.
But Enzo, are we going
to disregard his hunch?
You, Patricia…
-Mm?
-Come here.
Sit here. Give me that.
You need to take a break.
Here it is.
Will you add that to your to-do list too?
You just got better. Take a break.
I don't have time to rest.
I have a lot of work
and schoolwork waiting for me.
Well, at least you get to spend time
with Ms. D without working.
Are you taking your vitamins?
Don't push yourself too hard, huh?
Especially for your studies.
Just call me.
I can help you on your
Entrepreneurship Week.
You worry too much!
I still have both my hands and feet.
I can handle it.
You're overreacting.
Is it wrong to worry about you?
It's not that.
Vitamins. Okay?
And let me know if you need help.
Melody, I'll go there early.
Yes. Everything should be ready
for the Entrepreneurship Week.
There's still things missing?
Oh, well, that'll do.
I'll just do a follow-up tomorrow.
Okay, okay. Thank you. Bye.
Ah. Nothing.
Coffee doesn't suffice, huh?
You're cute, huh?
Just a bit OCD.
But reliable.
A gentleman.
Someone I can lean on.
You even understand my craziness.
It's like you always know
what to say when I get dramatic.
What was that?
Ah, nothing! That's uh…
Those are my lines.
I'm rehearsing for my audition.
-Lines?
-Mm-hmm.
-Nice lines, huh?
Maybe, I can audition there too.
For what role?
As your boyfriend.
Really?
Sir Enzo.
Boyfriend?
But seriously.
You want to give it a try?
-I'll go ahead, I'm late!
-Yes, go ahead.
Jena, I told you to arrange
the groceries last night!
I already bought it.
All you have to do is arrange it!
-Sis, I have school!
-Arrange it now!
I can't take care of that now!
I also have school! I even have an event.
It's important that I'm there early.
It's hard to commute. It's rush hour!
-Please, Jena!
-Patricia, I will meet
some friends so I can't be late!
Mom will get angry
if she sees the groceries lying there!
-Please, Jena.
-Hello.
-Where's Patricia?
-It's hard to get a ride!
-She's there.
-I'll fix it later!
Sis, I think you don't need
to commute anymore.
-Ah.
-I think you have a ride.
Sis!
He brought flowers!
He's handsome! Sis, go there!
Mm-hmm.
Hi.
Hello!
What is that for?
Nothing.
I just wanted to make your day.
Thank you.
Let's go?
-Hey, maybe we can get a ride too?
-Sis?
-Absolutely. Let's go!
-Come on! Let's go!
-Close the gate!
-Oh no.
-Wait a second.
-Mm?
For you.
What is this?
Open it!
YES, YOU PASSED THE AUDITION!
-Yes?
-Yes!
-Hey, hey!
That's your talent fee for now.
Uh, my name is Enzo.
Hi, Bro Enzo. I'm Jena.
I'm April.
Hello.
You and Patricia seem to be okay now.
You know, I'm glad that
she's listening to me somehow.
Oh! I have to go. I'm so sorry.
I don't have time to talk, Ricardo.
I have to go to Patricia.
Okay.
I have to give a talk at her school.
Mm.
I KNOW ABOUT EVERY MOVE
YOU MAKE. BE CAREFUL.
-Diana, what's the matter?
-Um…
Those bastards!
They're intimidating me again.
I'll call the police then.
No, no. I have to go.
I have to go to Patricia.
Wait! What if it wasn't just a phone call?
What if someone is waiting
for you out there?
Let's wait for the police
so that they can assess the threat.
No! If I wait, it will be too late.
I can't let Patricia down, Ricardo.
Not this time.
Enzo, is she still coming?
Ms. D said she's on her way.
We still have 30 minutes left.
You know that she always arrives one hour
before an event starts, right?
Maybe she just had to deal
with something first.
Enzo…
Hey, hey, hey.
Relax. She will come, okay?
-Wait, I'll go wait for her outside, okay?
-All right.
Benjie, what's taking you so long?
Ms. D, it looks like
there was an accident.
What?
Ms. D!
You crashed into my car!
-What will you do now?
-It's your fault!
-Ms. Dela Cruz.
-Ma'am.
Is Ms. Aragon already on her way?
Uh, I'll try calling her again.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Sorry, ma'am.
Hi, are we all good?
HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY
Patricia!
I'm here.
I'm here! I'm here now. I'm sorry, dear.
Uh…
Ms. D, meet Professor Connie.
Thank you for coming.
-I'm sorry I'm late.
-It's all right.
-It's a pleasure.
-Nice to meet you.
At a very young age,
I already knew what I really wanted to be,
and that was to be
a successful businesswoman.
To make my father proud.
So when I was given
this huge responsibility…
I didn't even flinch.
I've sacrificed so much…
to build and protect this business.
Maybe that's why I'm called the Chairmom.
If you were given a chance
to choose between being
a CEO and being a mother,
which one would you choose?
I don't regret working hard
because I'm not working hard
just for myself.
It's for my family
and the people who depend on me.
In a perfect world…
You wouldn't have to choose
between having a career…
and being a mother.
You can be both. You can do both.
And you should never have to apologize
for wanting to succeed.
In business, I have solved
every little problem.
Just like in business and motherhood…
you're going to make a lot of mistakes.
My father sent me to the most prestigious
business schools.
But, sadly…
I wasn't given a manual
on how to be a good mother.
And…
there were times…
that I struggled so much
trying to balance…
being a good leader, a good wife, and…
the kind of mother
that my daughter needed me to be.
In a world that asks so much of you,
do what gives you a purpose.
You know, I realized…
a bit late…
that my loved ones…
didn't always need me to fix everything
or to solve all their problems for them.
Sometimes, all they needed
was for me to be there.
To understand and to love them.
With all your achievements,
if you could give one piece of advice
to the younger generation,
what would it be?
So, my advice?
Be whomever you want to be in this world.
But…
as you build the life you want to have,
don't let go…
of the things that make up who you are.
We heard that your daughter
is studying here.
Yes, yes. She's right there.
Do you want to give her a message?
Do you want her to grow up to be like you?
I want her to be better than me.
Much better.
Actually, all I really want for her is…
for her to be whole.
For her to be happy.
And I hope that…
in all her wins or losses,
I want her to know that
I'm just right here for her.
-Thank you so much!
-Where's Patricia?
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Thank you.
Mom.
You came.
They're threatening you
because they're blaming you.
I think this is a new enemy.
What do you know
about the fire that happened back then?
I will tell you once more.
You don't have to go back
to what happened before.
You have no memory
of what happened back then.
We can correct what happened.
You're often together.
Is there something going on
between you and Mom?
I like Diana.
I want to be happy for Mom.
But something feels wrong.